{
    "id": "af34da513b474c488da46172332c7b50",
    "title": "Gerunds of participles exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "5763f97d054748848e234480ac8ceba3",
            "title": "Gerunds Or Participles",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "You are …………………. too much these days.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "smoking",
                        "smoked"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "There was a …………………… cigarette end in the ashtray.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "smoking",
                        "smoked"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Having …………………  for ten hours, I felt great.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "sleeping",
                        "slept"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Not …………………… what to do, I went home.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "knowing",
                        "known"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She went ……………………… out of the room.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "run",
                        "running"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………… stamps is a hobby of mine.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Collecting",
                        "collected"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I hate …………………. suitcases.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "packing",
                        "packed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She was angry at Susie …………………… to lie to her.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "trying",
                        "tried"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The roof was ………………… off in the storm.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "blown",
                        "blowing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The doctor suggested ………………….. a long holiday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "taking",
                        "taken"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}